Ajay has a
very good afternoon friends welcome back
to hard questions to drive safe mission
possible consonants characters kasana anonymous back with
toys set up question of the dead cells
picture with and question of the day in the
screenshots
are you can see all my screen the question zabar
in written during training you notice
royal coming under high speed in the opposite
side you will harm to indicate your
training wait for the michael to crops and
dental clinic 10s you have done this many
times honey lights S2 indicate you are talking
to you can read your answers which you see him
into lord when you can not be a
part of this and you can win exciting
prizes they request you to can join us
camp in along with your family friends
and will lock horns whoever you
want to see safe on everyday whom you share
vicky sadha school mission S2 amit
and rosary for two days decree dashrath on  The
road accident this please be a part of the
roads and
that bring change on Indian roads Arzoo Kin
you all the best wealth which twelfth day and
circle a question of the day and he is the
question period screen skin straight cut aapko
aapke face to all hai hum log jaate hain
aapke saath with le all new five questions
and you can be a part of 10 with me a
pin business top 10 and the bare rise free
mode switch on screen inch fog during tonic during
training you no disturb
he coming such high speed in opposite
side you will harm to indicate you are
talking with father Michael Clark Ross and
don't weekly toys this of damini times honey
lights S2 indicate you are doing a that
now you are turning on and there is a very false tonic
point you have noticed that
one of the options from the other side is coming at a very high
speed so what will you do at that
time let them indicate that
you are going to tone or else
Difficult to cross and a new ringtone of
wait that the vehicle with you is a
cross sign, after that
you will do which horoscope, which village, put 10
minutes time, now quickly tone because
you have done it many times before and then honey
lights will indicate you are trying, these
lights will turn on and you will tell them what you are going to do, so
quickly
connect yourself with your answer, Aslam, just do it and
you have a chance to win some exciting
prizes, your result is
that at 10:00 pm our show comes,
plain speaking, you
can enter your 123 in it, you have your pimples on it, they
announce delivery, after that
our questions start from 9:00 am, the
questions change every 2 hours,
those are our exams that we add to you
and they add to you with new questions,
so you have a chance to
win even more exciting prizes, there is still two more
Questions and left after 10 so you have a
chance to win we would request you to
please join this campaign with your
family friends and loved ones home you want to see
station road it is very important to be safe
under rule and this turning
point thing that we talked about in this, in this the
questions that you bring on this in Delhi are all related to roles
and we help zone to
make people aware that you are joining us so that
you become aware that when
we
start astrology on daily basis then are we doing the right thing
and this is also because if you are
becoming a part of it then you should always remember
that whatever you do, do it very thoughtfully, be aware that this should not cause any
harm to you or others or someone should
not become a victim of an accident, one carelessness can take anyone's
life on the road and this often happens with us
that we both are on point
and the other is riding the bike  If you want to
join, what will we do?
Tell us your
relationship status and if the answer is correct,
you have a chance to win these exciting
prizes. So be a part of this
truth. Safety is very important. This
question of ours will
run for 300% of every Motu for Mode to Go. So you
can be a part of this. Its
store business is in the top 10 and you can win
exciting prizes for yourself and
your love dynasty. Today is also Valentine's Day.
You can give tips for yourself and your loved ones. You can take
road safety measures. There can be
no better gift than that.
You are giving them safety. Now you
expect them to be safe, only then will you be able to be happy.
So, take care of your safety and the
safety of your loved ones.
Follow Rohit Shetty's rules every day.
Stay safe on the route yourself and let others
stay safe too. We know everything about
what to do and what not to do when you go out on the road.  Do
we follow those things?
If we don't,
we know what we should do.
It can cause traffic jams or it can
harm someone. So, we need to avoid those things and make
our daily life very safe.
We need to make them safe
because somewhere or the other, on a
daily basis, we are all connected to the roads. We all are connected to roads. So, it is
very important for all of us to be safe.
You know that 415 people
leave their homes and never come back. That
means exam generation and that means
people who are in bad shape. Most of the
people lose their loved ones. It often happens
that they are alone in the
morning portion of the road. That means they are
in a small family and they also have to decide for themselves.
That is why we say that
it is very important that you take care of the safety of yourself and your loved ones
and always
follow the road safety rules. If you are
not out of the house, then
remember, if you are riding a two-wheeler, it is
very important that you wear your helmet.
Helmet is always ISI.
Buy the brand, use it properly
and when you buy helmets, always
remember that you should choose it properly,
it should not be used much nor should it be a tattered one,
if it is used then if there is
any mishap or any accident then
that helmet will not be able to save you, if
it is not ISI marked then it will break,
if it is from a local company then if you buy it just to avoid a
challan then
it will not be able to save your life,
as I said that many people
buy helmets, they
buy the local helmets which are available on the roads and just because they do
not have a challan but they get proud that this is
not for the challan or for the police or for anyone else, these are safety
measures, this element is for your own
safety, the day this thing will become clear in our mind,
not that this road is
stuck, the road safety page is open, all the
rules and regulations which are made are
for our safety, that day we will be able to
make our life more safe
because we  We keep thinking that all this will
always be saved by switching on the alarm, there is a
policeman standing there or there is a cameraman, there are
many cameras installed and he will have to operate them on the route, that is why
we do not do that, we do
not follow the rules of our interest, then
we become careless in those matters,
if we do that then it will be illegal in that matter,
all these things are for our safety
and we have to do this, only then we will be able to understand
our road clearly, we
request you that whatever road safety
measures are there, you must
wear green chillies while going out and if you are
interested then you should
cross the routes only through crossings, cross like this
because you cannot apply brakes immediately and
if there is a foot overbridge on that route then
please use the overbridge,
use the underpass here and if
you are not able to find that and there is
no foot crossing near you then always
look at the road and cross carefully,
if you press the brakes immediately then
you will not miss it and if a vehicle is
coming at high speed then it will not be able to apply brakes  It
takes time to
plant the brain's reaction time
because it happens in motion and
sometimes those options like brakes are not applied
because it is a gadget, so you can take care of your safety
and make rules so that because of your mistake that
person might save you but who
knows because of your stupidity he might lose his life,
he might go and hit some lord's ball
or the
barricades on the side etc. and he might
not lose his life, so it is not that if
someone is driving, that is, if someone is driving, it is his
fault, anyone can make a mistake, so
you are making yourself responsible,
you have to see how you can protect yourself and others,
if you take
care of small people and we do
not make such mistakes every day, then you will be
able to save your life and the lives of your loved ones and will
also be able to keep others safe, so our entire
campaign is
related to road safety, which is not our entire
work, it is based on this, how can
we make people as safe as possible,
how can we make people more safe  If you can
set more and this date is read, when is
our dip, when is our dip, the date when is our dip is increasing every
day, but how can we use it, so
please give part of this campaign and bring together and
change the list in the chase on the road
to
yesterday morning jogging CEO on my school name the
question is visible in written during the opening you do
not disturb that kamikaze
high speed in the opposite side you will
see you have to concentrate and when you were about to turn,
you saw that another vehicle is
coming very fast
from the other side, so what will you do, at that time, phone
to indicate your turning, you will look at the phone and
tell them that you are about to join,
wait for the vehicle to divert your attention from the cycle, you will
wait and only
after that you will join or you will
turn on the previous Chauhan Asif in this many times quickly because you know
and you have done it many times before,
so these lights to indicate your
turning, so you will turn on these
lights in this part  And you tell them
that you are going to tone up, so as you
quickly you have time to ask
and you also mean that you have patience, you
can answer this question as quickly as possible, so this is a
daily basis question, this is what
we see in our life on a daily basis and the
roles we play now, so
tell us what you do at that time and
if you do not do this thing then whatever you do at that
time, think about it,
stop and think and then give your MP
mention on it, if we request you
and whatever you answer, like whatever you
feel is right, then please apply that thing,
follow it in your life
and help us in making your roles just
because it is very important to
keep yourself just and keep others safe and take
care of the makers of the festival,
so this is our question up to 300 favorites,
you can participate in it and up
to 80 fabrics you can participate in it today
our  Twelfth day is Andhra Vyalon with you with
this question name drive se
information possible yes-yes of western to
make it possible to Merta road safety
everyone needs to decrease the cover of
accidents inside please be a part of
this universe * Varna Kasana thank you so much
for day stay healthy stay tune love will be back after
to all with new only question
for timing thank you so much oo